[

    {
        "type": "vocab_meaning",
        "question": "甘い",
        "options": ["pahit", "manis", "asin", "asam"],
        "correct": 1,
        "subtext": "Pilih arti yang tepat"
    },
    {
        "type": "vocab_meaning",
        "question": "辛い",
        "options": ["pedas", "pahit", "manis", "hambar"],
        "correct": 0,
        "subtext": "Pilih arti yang tepat"
    },
    {
        "type": "vocab_meaning",
        "question": "苦い",
        "options": ["asin", "asam", "pahit", "enak"],
        "correct": 2,
        "subtext": "Pilih arti yang tepat"
    },
    {
        "type": "vocab_meaning",
        "question": "お湯",
        "options": ["air dingin", "air es", "air mendidih", "air panas"],
        "correct": 3,
        "subtext": "Pilih arti yang tepat"
    },
    {
        "type": "vocab_meaning",
        "question": "料理",
        "options": ["minuman", "bahan", "masakan", "alat"],
        "correct": 2,
        "subtext": "Pilih arti yang tepat"
    },
    {
        "type": "meaning_vocab",
        "question": "Rasa",
        "options": ["卵", "料理", "お湯", "味"],
        "correct": 3,
        "subtext": "Pilih kosakata yang tepat"
    },
    {
        "type": "meaning_vocab",
        "question": "Telur",
        "options": ["味", "卵", "苦手", "辛い"],
        "correct": 1,
        "subtext": "Pilih kosakata yang tepat"
    },
    {
        "type": "meaning_vocab",
        "question": "Mengaduk",
        "options": ["注ぐ", "混ぜる", "捨てる", "かける"],
        "correct": 1,
        "subtext": "Pilih kosakata yang tepat"
    },
    {
        "type": "meaning_vocab",
        "question": "Menuangkan",
        "options": ["注ぐ", "混ぜる", "捨てる", "かける"],
        "correct": 0,
        "subtext": "Pilih kosakata yang tepat"
    },
    {
        "type": "meaning_vocab",
        "question": "Kenyang",
        "options": ["もう１つ", "お腹がいっぱい", "どんどん", "苦手"],
        "correct": 1,
        "subtext": "Pilih kosakata yang tepat"
    },
    {
        "type": "vocab_reading",
        "question": "味",
        "options": ["たまご", "からい", "あじ", "にがて"],
        "correct": 2,
        "subtext": "Pilih cara baca yang tepat"
    },
    {
        "type": "vocab_reading",
        "question": "料理",
        "options": ["にがて", "りょうり", "すこし", "からい"],
        "correct": 1,
        "subtext": "Pilih cara baca yang tepat"
    },
    {
        "type": "vocab_reading",
        "question": "卵",
        "options": ["たまご", "あじ", "りょうり", "おゆ"],
        "correct": 0,
        "subtext": "Pilih cara baca yang tepat"
    },
    {
        "type": "vocab_reading",
        "question": "苦手",
        "options": ["すこし", "おゆ", "にがて", "あまい"],
        "correct": 2,
        "subtext": "Pilih cara baca yang tepat"
    },
    {
        "type": "reading_meaning",
        "question": "おいしい",
        "options": ["tidak enak", "enak", "hambar", "pahit"],
        "correct": 1,
        "subtext": "Pilih arti yang tepat"
    },
    {
        "type": "reading_meaning",
        "question": "まずい",
        "options": ["enak", "hambar", "tidak enak", "manis"],
        "correct": 2,
        "subtext": "Pilih arti yang tepat"
    },
    {
        "type": "reading_meaning",
        "question": "たまごやき",
        "options": ["telur mata sapi", "telur rebus", "sup telur", "telur dadar gulung"],
        "correct": 3,
        "subtext": "Pilih arti yang tepat"
    },
    {
        "type": "reading_meaning",
        "question": "からあげ",
        "options": ["ayam goreng", "ayam bakar", "sate ayam", "sup ayam"],
        "correct": 0,
        "subtext": "Pilih arti yang tepat"
    },
    {
        "type": "reading_meaning",
        "question": "きのこ",
        "options": ["sup", "puding", "jamur", "kaldu"],
        "correct": 2,
        "subtext": "Pilih arti yang tepat"
    },
    {
        "type": "reading_meaning",
        "question": "プリン",
        "options": ["puding", "sup", "jamur", "kaldu"],
        "correct": 0,
        "subtext": "Pilih arti yang tepat"
    }

]